[{"answer": "I've been to so many.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "What was the greatest part?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Welcome.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "You don't really take prisoners, do you?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "I never thought of that.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Is there a theme that you see in your life?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "She's in her 90s, right?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "She thinks so.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "And she's been like most mothers -- she's been your biggest fan and critic over the years?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "The good stuff?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Kevin Costner is as different from Anthony Hopkins as night to day, but they are both extraordinary to work with.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Which of all the actors you've worked with has been the best?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Charlie Sheen was a young man when I worked with him on two films.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "I lost track of Charlie in the mid-'80s, late '80s.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "But what did you feel, looking at this guy, who you'd worked so closely with before?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "I mean, taking --", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "In the old days, in the old days, you know?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Robert Downey was pretty wild.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "All of you at your peak, who would be the greatest guest, you'd have to a party?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "It's not going to go away.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "What is the simplistic answer, do you think, to the global drugs problem?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "And the U.S. -- and the Mexican economy would die without it because they need the money, it goes into their legitimate economy.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "And it hasn't worked, has it?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "If you killed the -- if you declared -- if there were no war on drugs, the Mexican economy would have to -- would be radically -- would dry up.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "-- what do you do?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Do you ever wish you hadn't done that particular scene, the greed is good scene?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Couldn't believe it.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "-- took it at face value, didn't they?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Some are, yes.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Are they effective?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Oh!", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "When you see your country, $16 trillion in debt and everyone's squabbling over what most people say, is an insubstantial solution, what do you think?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "And do you think it would help if more policy makers in America had experienced war?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Well, first of all I learned to survive.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "What was it you learned about yourself, when you were in Vietnam?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "I think your theme about war, generally, throughout all of your movies, is incredibly important, actually?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "I'm not going to give away ending but -- because that's a spoiler --", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "I think it's hard.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "You've tried it lately, Piers?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Just from what you said about her!", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "How do you know?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "She comes from a totally different world.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "I'm equally astonished and disappointed by myself.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "If you were describing yourself to somebody, who had never heard anything about you, what would be the honest description?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Put it this way, I think this life is a mystery and it's also a hunt for the truth, a hunt for what works for you and you express yourself as you go, sometimes badly, sometimes well.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Why astonished?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "In the same way because, gosh!", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Why disappointed?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "No!", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "I would say -- I mean, yes, I mean, if it's -- you can jazz up it a bit, can't you?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Dramatist, if you want or, you know, but that sums it up.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "That's simple descriptive word, filmmaker, would be enough for you?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "He was a good citizen, I hope!", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Nothing personal?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "This teddy bear.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "How are you, sir?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "I told them that the bear has a potty mouth.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "How do you break their little hearts and say they can't go?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "White trash name.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "What's her name?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Wait, was it any one of those names with a \"Lynn\" after it?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "You just came in and went -- is that true?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Did you get it right every time?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "A lot of practice.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "OK, how?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Yeah, plenty.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Any names?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Russell Crowe is extremely prepared.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Who are the ones you look at and go, that's where I want to be?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Do you like that versatility?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Can you do that accent?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Yes, unfortunately, yes.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Would you be the mentor?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "I would probably choose not quitting school because that's when everything started to go downhill.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "When you look back over this amazing career you've had, with all the twists and turns, if I had the power to let you relive one moment again, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "She's very proud me.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "What did she say about you doing it?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "I'm very good at math.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "What have you found you're good at and not so good at?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Counting money, isn't it?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 692, "question": "Your mother must find it extraordinary, what's happened to you, doesn't she?", "qSentId": 691}, {"answer": "Yeah, we're friendly.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Are these friends of yours?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "Certainly.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "Was there a moment, a cathartic moment, where you just woke up and went, I'm done with that?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "Did you have a red devil on your shoulder that whispers in your ear occasionally?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "No temptation to suddenly go crazy again?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "That gives you enough?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 758, "question": "Is it because you know where you came from?", "qSentId": 757}, {"answer": "I'm going to go down and pull the lever, you know.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 767, "question": "Where are you sitting?", "qSentId": 766}, {"answer": "No, I was not.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "Were you there?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "No, I was.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "Not invited?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "You know, you can cut a check and go.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 780, "question": "You even turned down dinner with the president and George Clooney?", "qSentId": 779}, {"answer": "I was nervous about it.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 835, "question": "It was such a great role, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 834}, {"answer": "A bit awkward.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 840, "question": "When you are in the Jacuzzi, semi-naked with Burt Reynolds, fun or awkward?", "qSentId": 839}, {"answer": "He's a great guy, yeah.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 846, "question": "Is he a good guy?", "qSentId": 845}, {"answer": "One sixty five to 205, 45.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 868, "question": "ORGAN: Sorry, give it to me again?", "qSentId": 867}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120629pmt", "aSentId": 895, "question": "It comes out the weekend, right?", "qSentId": 894}]